okay
well welcome everyone thanks for joining
it's september 16th and we are
in
the third meeting for cohort two
we're on our second discussion of
chapter one in the textbook
so
this is our
um
closing
discussion on chapter one
which is going to be just our jumping
off point into
the following chapters
we'll go to the questions page where i
saw some
questions were submitted
uh and we can also look at other
areas
like just the chapter notes more
generally
but before we go to the questions is
there any just remarks that people would
like to share on chapter one
and then otherwise i'll i'll make one
short note about another resource
i'll be watching the hand raising too
well first maybe i'll just share this
other resource
and i'll it's already added to the
resources section and i'll put it in the
nearby
it's called pools of insight it's from
however
um the author is still
like around and when i emailed uh
them
yeah this is the the most recent version
and the document is called pools of
insight
um a previous version i guess was called
knowledge hydrant
but again this is the most recent
version even though it's
almost as old as some of us might be um
and it's based around alexander's
christopher alexander's pattern language
which may be familiar to some it's a
it's a very unique
book
and it speaks to archetypes in
architecture and design
and talks about how there's composition
of patterns and
makes a language and a grammar for that
and that kind of a pattern language
approach has been built on in many other
settings and this
work
is a very interesting application of
pattern languages to learning groups
i think
going through it
could be interesting for anybody who's
just
curious about this
approach of pattern languages and
learning groups
and also we're very interested to apply
this
more intentionally
as we continue to iterate on the
learning groups format
in active inference institute
textbook groups for years to come and
new textbooks to come and so on
um
just looking at the titles
there's a lot of insight
like the book is a knowledge hydrant
how do we even approach that
the group is like a pool of insight how
do we approach that you know how are we
going to integrate
our individual study
with group
dialogue so
not
much more to say on this today
but if anyone's like excited about that
it would be awesome to hear their um
how they see these patterns playing out
because a lot of them
um
speak to what we want to cultivate
in this group
okay
going to the questions page
there's still also time for people to be
adding in
a
a brock i put it in the um nearby not
the room i'll add it there too
and it's also in resources you can just
look up you know
fools
you'll find it
people may still add more
questions
to the page but we have some really rich
questions provided already
so we'll start with a smaller one
in relation to perception action loops
the book states the possibilities for
control and adaptation are plentiful but
very few are useful
i'm not sure how useful is being used
here useful for evolution survival what
determines useful
page four
what does anyone
see or think
so i don't know i would just venture to
jump up the cliff and guess that maybe
the authors mean like full
maintenance of
the non-equilibrium steady state density
or like existence
just to guess though
all right what's the non-equilibrium
steady state
it is like the the balance of
of all things that we find ourselves in
as living creatures so like you know i'm
a human
i
have you know a certain amount of cells
tissues and organs i have
a temperature that i
expect to find my body at and like a
range of temperatures that i can survive
in i need a certain concentration of
oxygen my blood oxygen needs to be
maintained at that level so just like
all of the things that like i need to
have a certain amount of water
like like all of the things that
contribute to
me being able to persist
as in my non-equilibrium steady state so
it's like you know if you're in
equilibrium as a biological organism you
are dead
so
um
life is maintained in this
non-equilibrium steady state
and i think that we have to
be able to maintain that
and maybe the authors just need
maintenance
useful in the maintenance of that
non-equilibrium steady state
great
yes so one
qualitative way to frame it is with
persistence in survival
not saying this is the only meaning of
utility
but persistence and survival are
imperatives for
things
again using thing in the active
inference sense as like the particular
states
the blanket states and the internal
for things
that are to persist
then they have to at least be acting
in a survivable way things that are
acting as to not persist are not going
to be around for long
things that are acting as if they are to
persist will be repeatedly measured
they'll be repeatedly observed
by others
or they'll be repeatedly observing
themself in the autopoetic case
and then blue brought in um
a nice
term from the actin pontology
which is the non-equilibrium steady
state
and by like mousing over you can see
some of the definitions that have been
provided
and this is all part of the work that
people can contribute to if they want to
be improving definitions and so on
and the first definition is
slightly more technical
the second
definition is slightly less technical
and it just says it's a system with
dynamics that are unchanging or out of
stationarity in some state
so
um that doesn't mean the system is
static or unchanging
it's like a dynamic balance
so we can think about like the length of
a bone isn't a dynamic balance between
um being built up and being broken down
and so that maintenance of a
non-equilibrium steady state is
maintained
kind of like homeostasis or like body
temperature blood sugar etc like blue
mentioned in the long run
um
and that may take energy that may be
like an exothermic process to maintain
there
but it also is maintaining a stasis in
some other respect
um
so again few are useful
what is this first part why are the
possibilities for control and adaptation
plentiful and why does that present an
issue ali
uh i was just gonna mention the three
phases of bayesian mechanics
i mean
mode matching dynamics mode tracking
dynamics and path tracking dynamics
from which
active inference dynamics
falls in the category of the path
tracking dynamics
but
unlike the first two types i mean mode
matching dynamics and mode tracking
dynamics
which
requires density
i mean which requires ness assumption
uh
the
path tracking dynamics
yeah that's it uh is present is
described as a known as assumption
dynamics so
if we
extend the active inference framework to
include not only
the
i mean nest preserving dynamic to all
the other kinds of agents which
uh just do this kind of path tracking
dynamic then uh i guess we would not
need uh
any kind of nest preserving
mechanism
to do these kind of action perception
the perception action loops
very
interesting
um this is
bringing in another resource which is an
excellent contemporary resource
um
which is some of the recent work of
ramstead at all
on on bayesian mechanics
and it's it's unpacked in guest stream
23.1
so that that's one very nice resource um
and
coming back to what blue set about
non-equilibrium steady states we can
think about one case as being like
there's a fixed point
and we want just
simple convergence to a fixed point
and that might be useful like if utility
in a situation is defined as we want the
plate to be balanced on the stick
and we want it the plate to be as tall
as possible that's like kind of a
classical control theory setting
then we might want to have that one
fixed mode and that's our utility it's
not some sort of like absolute
theological utility it's just saying
like within this domain or aspect or
dimension
utility is going to be defined by
reducing the divergence
to some fixed mode
alternatively there could be a dynamic
mode following
like um there's going to be some cursor
on your screen and you're just going to
be seeking to follow it
and in that case
utility is going to be defined by the
divergence minimization to a moving mode
and then the last case is this path
matching which does introduce some um
more powerful in general
mathematics like um the gauge formalism
and in that case the path
distances are being divergence minimized
and
it brings in a super important topic
that that um
next i i um we'll turn to brock to give
a thought on
which is this idea of utility and
pragmatic value as divergence
minimization
we're gonna come back to that but brock
feel free to add what you would like
about this if you want
um
i mean
it's page four so
it might be there's a lot more
like as we go through this that will
kind of start helping to connect dots
but um
in the kind of biological
uh homeostasis can like example the
blues
um
there are just a lot of things that you
could do
that would not be
like you're saying in that context
useful
for the organism
um and there are things that you could
do that
are useful maybe in a moment but they're
not kind of
meta useful like or like creating more
usefulness or something like this for
the organism right
um
but there are are things that that an
organism might do that like um just kind
of put it in a place where all the
things it could do
are just significantly more likely to be
useful
and so one of those things that it might
do is like go find forage for like a
place where food is plentiful and then
if it gets hungry and it just starts to
go look then necessarily it will kind of
start finding food more readily than if
it hadn't gone to that patch or you know
humans we build houses
or some sort of structure that protects
us from the elements and then
you know um
if we oversleep
or whatever like a wild animal doesn't
get us and neither does the cold or the
maybe
in the same way like um so
that's
um
the language that the book is going to
use around that is about
um
free energy reduction like free energy
minimization
which is just to say
in some really
coarse grain not completely correct way
that like it's just taking
a lot of choices off of the table a lot
of actions
that um
would not help
would not
cause the thing to persist or
find more usefulness or
so
and and the
other two words here that i'm using a
pragmatic epistemic value
is the epistemic value is kind of like
going to
find the like foraging for the food
and then the
the pragmatic value is like
like actually eating getting the food or
something like that um not
exactly but
very rough
analogous sort of
i don't know if that's helpful but
that's awesome thank you
yeah many
pieces here so
first you mentioned like the state space
of possible
moves
which is what is being suggested here
with the first part of the sentence the
possibilities for control and adaptation
are plentiful
so we can think about those in terms of
affordances
which are relational capacities for
action
and the set of possible moves or
affordances might be large
however only like a vanishingly small
subset of them
might be useful
and then part of the challenge that's
pointed to
is that um
there's a recursive nature of the cycle
so it's not like we can just
say well you know pawn to e4 is just
simply a good move
because there's probably situations
where that like wins you the game and
there's probably situations where that
loses the game
so
within the utility defined by like a
game
there's
already immense
challenges in exploring these like
branching trees of outcomes
and just evaluating them under any
metric period
so
how
can we evaluate
perception
and action
and
planning
the idea that's going to come into play
is action and planning as divergence
minimization
this can be contrasted
with the notion of perception cognition
action planning etc as reward
maximization
reward maximization
is equivalent to pragmatic value
maximization
utility optimization
is pragmatic value um and we're going to
see this reflected soon
in
some of the equations to come in the
next chapters
but for chapter one we're still
addressing this like um qualitatively
pragmatic value is like
the task
you know time on task
um if
if
the pragmatism in the mountain climbing
example is climbing the mountain
then pragmatic value is like every inch
you take up the mountain
epistemic value would be
reducing your uncertainty about how to
achieve pragmatic value
and so
in that way
the free energy functional
which encompasses both pragmatic and
epistemic value
allows
a more adept navigation of explore and
exploit
because under a reward maximization
framework
it's very easy to like you know
turn the speaker up to 11 set the phaser
to stun
and pursue local pragmatic value
however
all of these second order heuristics
need to come into play
to reintroduce like novelty bonuses
curiosity as a second level on to this
um reward first pragmatic value first
foundation
and in contrast
the imperatives
for
action and
perception in active inference are going
to be built around not reward
maximization but
free energy minimization or relative
free energy reduction as mentioned
and that's going to be composed of
there's going to be multiple ways to
break that down what the free energy
functional is
but
it is going to often come down to
um a pragmatic element in an epistemic
element
um the pragmatic element
is going to look like again we're
just beginning
to come into these sections
the pragmatic value
is going to look like a reduction of
divergence
between preferences
and observations
so instead of saying
well the most rewarding body temperature
for me is 37
and i'm maximizing reward by staying at
that's a reward maximization perspective
on temperature homeostasis
a divergence minimization perspective
surprise minimization perspective
on body temperature homeostasis
is
i expect and prefer
to find myself at 37
and i'm going to undertake policy to
reduce my surprise about finding myself
at 37.
so when i'm at 37 i'll be minimally
surprised
and as i get further i will be more and
more surprised
and then i will take pragmatic action to
climb that hill
as well as epistemic actions to find out
how to climb that hill
but we're going to be getting back to 37
by reducing the divergence between
preferences and outcomes
rather than getting to 37
by like
winning and trying to maximize reward
which is the only
fundamental um
ontology
for reward based learning
so that's how many people have in that
um
basal
relationship
between pragmatic and epistemic value
and active inference
that's where many people have found
space to explore like curiosity
and novelty and a lot of other things
will open up once we first start to
explore
how pragmatic and epistemic value
are like connected and as coequal
in the imperatives for active inference
agents and then there'll be even more
fun things to come like
again when we realize that pragmatic
value isn't
maximizing rewards simply
it's reducing
the divergence relative to expectations
so it's like again not um we're playing
chess and we're trying to maximize our
points and minimize their points
but we have an optimistic
trajectory or set of expectations and
then we're going to reduce the
divergence such that that is realized
so what determines useful
as with
many other questions there's like a
limited answer that's so limited that it
may not feel like an answer
which is like again if we're balancing a
plate on a stick
we may define utility as keeping the
plate up
if we were climbing a mountain we may
define utility in that limited dimension
as getting to the top of the mountain
that may feel like too narrow because we
might think well like but the person
balancing the plate i mean they have to
have a salary and they have to breathe
and have blood sugar and stuff like that
so
the limited answer
is like sort of just staying within the
bounds of our model and the dimensions
that we're considering
and then part of this iterative modeling
process
which especially starts to be introduced
in the second half of the book
but also is reflected by people's
experience
in
other modeling areas including
qualitative modeling areas like so then
it's okay so now we have the plate
balancer
and their blood sugar
and then are we still missing something
relative to the real world are we as
modelers still being surprised by what
happens
now we need to consider something else
so
that's like the limited
answer
which is utility is situational and
dimensional
in a narrow sense
and then in perhaps a slightly more like
miso or macro sense
utility
um or at least like um
a cousin
or a proxy of utility
is survival and persistence
because without survival and persistence
you're not going to be around
to even have that debate about what's
useful
so it is kind of like a prerequisite or
an enabling feature
of any
dimensional or like sort of one aspect
you know if you want to
be in the game
[Music]
to to realize any specific kind of
utility being in the game is like that
meta
utility
which
brock pointed towards with like
different um
behaviors and phenomena ranging from
epistemic foraging to um
niche construction and like building a
house
any other thoughts on utility
what determines useful
okay
this looks like a great
long question so i'm going to just bring
it down so we can kind of break it into
sections
um
can anyone describe
the neat and scruffy
distinction
it's on page five
ollie yes
it's again related to
the high road on the low road
i mean uh
they've described the high road as
the needs
perspective or the needs approach
and the low road as the scrappy one uh
probably because high road begins with
some
some established
[Music]
postulates and
let's say
without going into
a bottom-up approach and beginning with
the fundamental
uh
principles and then developing
uh the propositions
uh from there but beginning with
established propositions and then
uh
somehow
chopping it off or
somehow going into a much more granular
level in terms of its fundamental
constituents
thank you excellent
i i
find this paragraph to be a very nice
point
which is
we can think of two extreme
ends
of a um kind of like research program or
epistemic ecosystem
one would be
every single neural process
you know acetylcholine synapses
neuro hormones being circulated in this
part every single
physiological piece could have its own
theory i mean they could have their own
department they could have their own
university
um and same for every cognitive
mechanism we could have a separate
bespoke model
with no interoperability at all there's
no reason why it has to
between um attention cognition
perception action social interaction
communication
anticipation planning
we could have bespoke theories
and somebody might suggest that that is
like preferable in their eye
whether for utility or for aesthetic
reasons
in their words that would lead to a
proliferation of theories in fields such
as the above
with little hope for their unification
another perspective
is that despite their diverse
manifestations the central aspects of
behavior cognition adaptation
in living organisms are amenable to
coherent explanation from first
principles
so in other words could we start with
first principles
can explain or explore what those are
but can we start with first principles
and then see
different biological processes
and different cognitive mechanisms
as
being
under a common
umbrella or under a common ontology or
addressable by a shared model
and
then to come back to the question um
because this is a nice
key point of this uh chapter it's uh
alluding to roger shank introducing this
neat versus scruffy distinction
and then as ali suggested this does map
to the high road and the low road
which um
[Music]
are mapped out in figure 1.2
and so
the neats
are like the lumpers
they're finding
unity
in
heterogeneity
and then the scruffies
are
like
embracing the heterogeneity by focusing
on details that demand dedicated
explanations
i mean how can we have a model of all
synapses when the acetylcholine synapses
are so different than the dopamine
synapses and then we'll need a third
model
or a third paper to describe when
there's both acetylcholine and dopamine
at the same synapse so that's like the
scruffy bottom up
embracing the heterogeneity of nature
and then the neat
is coming from the top down
or from the high road
and finding unification across that
diversification
brock
um sorry i just read this whole question
and i don't want to kind of
blow past
um getting into the details of each but
i want to try to maybe
from where you started there kind of
uh
thread uh
the needle there too to the end of
what's kind of being asked here is that
well he's he's in the context of these
you know uh bottom up
kind of
less
more explanatory but less meaningful and
the top down kind of more meaningful but
maybe in some cases less explanatory or
something like this
um
like how
do
we look at active inference or where
does it sit in relation to
all these other
um theories and models of
um
mind body cognition etc
and specifically in in fristen's um
essay uh the desert landscape here um
he's got a quote about fep kind of
subsuming all other
theories as
not some prediction but just that as
they kind of take one at a time here
they
have kind of just happened to be
commensurate and be describable
in some way here by fep and so
is that kind of like
meaningless
i lost you rock i'm not sure if that was
me
hmm
you
well sorry about this not sure what is
literally happening with my internet
loading okay
yep
uh kind of a source of the confusion for
most people about
what exactly what does active inference
exactly explain or uh and what's the
nature of the explanation there
can you um
copy paste that
that's a good response and i think
that's
uh
i've appended uh that response to the
pdf that i've uploaded
the
course's page
i was just i was just going to say that
that you know the desert landscape being
left there is
is kind of like a new niche that looks
maybe barren today but if we
continue maybe
it's not so barren maybe there are
adjacent things that are
that emerge from that niche being
constructed that cultural lens
being used that we look out and see
something different that we weren't
expecting
sorry about my
strange absence
um
bronwyn i think
okay yeah brock
yeah
are you daniel uh john
and you are talking learners
yeah i can't hear i'm gonna read life
in a more simple frame from my my
perspective which is not as advanced as
anyone here in the discussion but it's
but it's more from from
exactly uh the descriptions you've been
or what you've been talking about
has made it a bit more clear in a way
i'm not sure about the high road and the
low road sort of bottom up bottom down
thing but you know there's a lot of
theories about everything
um
but what was what came through then to
me was that with fep and active
inference it's a bit
um like it hasn't been fully explored
like it's it's um
that it's something where we're
actually investigating ourselves so we
don't actually know what we're going to
come up with
um
a bit like the sort of elephant with a
whole lot of people blind people trying
to work out what the elephant is
and and not actually
getting a grasp of the whole thing
and um
which makes it something that's going to
that still as someone said still
evolving still actually developing into
whatever it will be eventually
um
yeah which is which is helpful for my
for my question in terms of
if it's um
if it's going to
consume every other theory
um
makes it a little bit too grand and a
little bit
too much i think
i don't know if i'm making sense but um
it's quite a complex um
point
yeah i i think that that is
um
that's that is a very common response
and it's still i mean
when you say you're not as advanced as i
mean uh we're just using words we've
learned over the last
two months maybe
some of us um speaking personally um so
but um
you know it's
again there's this question like oh if
it describes everything
or you know and it's unfalsifiable then
what what does that mean you know it's
that's how is that helpful or what is
the use there i think
what what you keyed in on this sort of
evolving that we don't know quite yet
and how ali um called attention to that
response from carl
of a kind of cultural lenses being
developed like that that is
kind of like niche construction that is
that is us figuring out what is the
extent of this niche
where does fap apply where does active
inference apply like really well
yeah and then where does
daniel always uses linear regression
because it's so easy to
grasp at like
there's many cases where you know maybe
active inference maybe some magical
process is happening but
wow linear regression works really well
you know so
maybe
you know active inference applies but
it's a lot of work and linear regression
works really good right
um so there are certainly
i would expect you know boundaries
to where the pragmatic use like the
usefulness of it is not
um
it doesn't um continue there's some
drop-off redu yeah so
we don't know what that is precisely yet
i certainly don't i don't know if
somebody else does but
um it's it's a question that's being
explored and i don't yeah i think we
just will figure that out
um
over time through exploring and finding
where that desert you know ends kind of
or
slowly turns back into an oasis for us
to forage in
nice thank you for this um
discussion
i do love the linear regression i mean
imagine if i said really numbers you
think you're going to be able to
describe apples and oranges
with numbers or height and weight i mean
could two things be more different than
time and height and weight you really
think a linear regression is going to
cut through that
um so
sometimes
modeling and statistics overall
can feel like they're encompassing a lot
and then especially when there's so much
philosophy
and reflection and like relational
thinking
in the mix
it truly can converge on what feels like
a theory of everything
and um
one great video is um from a channel
called theories of everything
by kurt jeimungul
and um it's with carl first and there's
several with carl
and so that is tackled head on
and i don't exactly
um
recall
whether he goes this direction but
the the the um quintessentially
fristonian twist
is yeah we are talking about everything
everything
that for you
is in this sort of like process object
dialectic
it is realizing a non-equilibrium steady
state
otherwise you wouldn't call it a thing
so whatever it is that separates that
thing
from what is not that thing
is like a blanket
and if you're gonna say it's a fuzzy
blanket well
there's
some blanket index and there's a space
for that discussion as well
um but when we're talking about things
as they are
and or
as we model them
we can put them into a framework of
particular things
and that's the free energy principle for
a particular physics
also known as the bayesian mechanics
so it it does take a slightly different
approach
and then um what will
active inference converge upon
or move between these are
definitely
open and developing questions
and and also i i like what like about
the desert and the oasis because
the desert is alive as well
but
it's it's a reference to this um to
quine's desert landscape
um
and some of that work which has been
referenced
so
very um
interesting and then there's also like a
sort of interpersonal
approach slash
like rhetoric
like is
this presented as
are you presenting actin from the high
road
well all things need to resist
dissipation
so that's why we're using
non-equilibrium steady states to
describe how things exist
and those kinds of systems have to be
doing something that either is active
inference or that we can describe as
active inference
and starting with an imperative of
persistence
or
coming from the low road and thinking
about
instances
and how we can model what they're doing
using bayesian methods
and many times
people will find resonance with either
or both of those roads
and um
there's a huge amount of ontology
mapping
availabilities
for people to connect different theories
to each other
and also with ali and jakob and ander
well next month with the bayesian
mechanics
discussion
there
we'll we'll tackle this beijing
mechanics question
head on
and um
so it's just
i mean year after year and month after
month there's a lot to
learn and understand here and sometimes
the the philosophers
um outrun and anticipate
where things may
go
and then sometimes the writing and the
genre
can feel like something has already been
achieved like well there's already been
a synthesis of an activism an act of
inference
or it can feel like something that is
being um
doubted
is like a conclusive statement that it
cannot be addressed
markov blankets cannot address physical
interfaces
so
sometimes lifted from the modeling
there can be
writing and conversation
that might seem like it is like more or
less confident about the status or
future or past
of this area
which is like
what
motivates this kind of like reading
between the lines
and between the citations
and also a deflationary
modeling approach
where like
um
uh
um we don't know
you know it's still it's still in
evolution as to
to what to what it does but it sounds
as if it'll evolve into explaining some
things but not all things i suppose
that's where i've got to at the moment
at this point
yeah and just
you know the overriding i'm not sure
that's
i wouldn't worry about it overriding
um theories or you know things that kind
of already are useful
um right it's you know
um
relativity doesn't make you know
newton's
uh laws irrelevant
right
so
um
where that boundary is specifically is a
difficult question right now but i think
the vast majority of theory models of
these cognition are not that are you
know historically been useful are not
being thrown out they're just being
we're trying to connect them right so
i would also just add to that um there's
like the instrumentalist debate versus
the realest debate
and i think that um
you know the
act of inference is not necessarily
to be taken as this is not the way that
it is
more that it's a tool that we can use in
our in our toolbox and so i don't know
that it invalidates any other theory
um but it is um
just another another
tool in the toolbox right another thing
that we can use to model things and
definitely like there are some things
that active inference or at least as i
see it it doesn't explain yet like
um
like self-sacrificing behavior
right like like it doesn't necessarily
explain that yet but maybe if you look
across different temporal skills that
that's like possible or like in yeah
like negative harm and harmful like
self-harm so active inference i don't
think
um maybe we'll ever successfully model
that but also like one more thing i just
want to mention um i don't think anyone
here or i don't want to speak for
everyone but i don't think anyone in the
classroom today feels like they're at
the top of that learning curve
so um like i've been studying active
inference for like years already and i
still feel like maybe i'm in the long
tail end of the trail on the way up the
mountain so
um just just just know that it's
definitely a process
yeah i think i've realized that
i mean i've been reading about it for a
few years but um
and in relationship to to to what i do
um as a i'm an alexander technique
teacher so
i'm looking at it from that perspective
and just seeing how it fits in
um and so it comes up against other uh
motor control
theories and
you know i mean to say something really
simple is
uh the idea that we
that we don't have motor commands we
have predictions um
just the difference between that and if
i was going to put forward active
inference to my colleagues then
then
how do i
substantiate that or how do i explain
that this is
just a question in my mind i suppose do
i say that you know the motor command
thing's out the window and it's all
uh prediction or do i just say
this is a possibility this is one idea
yeah so that's a great point
great
point is that daniel
yeah
any
funny i can i can hear you though so
it's on the recording um anyone else
have anything asked comments or
questions
nice
it's it's great
yes go ahead
yeah
so i exchanged
some emails with the thomas parr
because i went through the book and
[Music]
i
you know i noticed some things that
may have been
some typos or some or ask him some some
questions and so i
i compiled the document on overleaf with
these points and questions and it was a
very kind
to
answer and to provide answers and
about also some clarification of some
questions
so
i'm i sent him an email and asked him if
he was okay
to share it with the group
to share the document with the group and
he hasn't answered yet but i'm pretty
sure he will
consent and then
you know
thank you so in this errata section
here's where we've um
have um a handful of uh typos and
ambiguities and i'll make a subpage
and um
you'll have full control
so just anything you want to do in this
subpage just do it
okay um
all right well
great time sorry about my strange
internet just
disrupts
beyond belief
but
we did it
i'll uh upload this
soon
and uh
enjoy
reading through chapter two
please add
any question
the most basic and the most confirmatory
to the most speculative every question
will be really amazing to see for
chapter two so
thanks everyone and see you soon